A Guide to the Records of the Photographs of XXX, 1990-1994
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Photographs of XXX, 1990-1994
The Library of Virginia
35539
5 cu. ft. (10 boxes)
XXX
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from
Biographical Information
BIOGRAPHY
Scope and Content
Photographs, 1990-1994,
Arrangement
This collection is arranged numerically by photograph number.
Contents List
- 90-0083, Governor Wilder lights State Christmas tree and holds Open House at the Mansion, 12/14/1990
- 90-0085, Governor Wilder lights State Christmas tree and holds Open House at the Mansion, 12/14/1990
- 90-0086, Governor Wilder lights State Christmas tree and holds Open House at the Mansion, 12/14/1990
- 90-0087, Governor Wilder lights State Christmas tree and holds Open House at the Mansion, 12/14/1990
- 90-0088, Governor Wilder lights State Christmas tree and holds Open House at the Mansion, 12/14/1990
- 90-0089, Governor Wilder addresses the General Assembly Money Committee, 12/17/1990
- 90-0090, Governor Wilder addresses the General Assembly Money Committee, 12/17/1990
- 90-0091, Governor Wilder receives a Bible from the Gideons, 12/17/1990
- 90-0092, Family practice of Blackstone receives a reward and it was presented by Governor Wilder, 12/18/1990
- 90-0093, Officer Floyd Mann retirement party, Officer Mann retires from the Capitol Police after 37 years, 2/28/1990
- 90-7450, Candids of reception at the Governor's Mansion, 1/3/1990
- 90-7451, Candids of reception at the Governor's Mansion, 1/3/1990
- 90-7452, Candids of reception at the Governor's Mansion, 1/3/1990
- 90-7476, Presentation to staff by Governor of World Atlas, 1/8/1990
- 90-7481, Photos of rooms in Executive Mansion, 1/9/1990
- 90-7482, Photos of rooms in Executive Mansion, 1/9/1990
- 90-7483, Photos of rooms in Executive Mansion, 1/9/1990
- 90-7484, Photos of rooms in Executive Mansion, 1/9/1990
- 90-7485, Photos of rooms in Executive Mansion, 1/9/1990
- 90-7486, Photos of rooms in Executive Mansion, 1/9/1990
- 90-7487, Photos of rooms in Executive Mansion, 1/9/1990
- 90-7488, Photos of rooms in Executive Mansion, 1/9/1990
- 90-7489, Photos of rooms in Executive Mansion, 1/9/1990
- 90-7490, Photos of rooms in Executive Mansion, 1/9/1990
- 90-7505, Conference room, reception area, Governor's office, 1/11/1990
- 90-7528, Cabinet Swearing, 1/14/1990
- 90-7529, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7530, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7531, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7532, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7533, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7534, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7535, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7536, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7537, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7538, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7539, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7540, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7541, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7542, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7543, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7544, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7545, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7546, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7547, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7548, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7549, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7551, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7553, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7554, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7555, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7556, Inauguration activities for Wilder, Beyers and Terry, 1/13/1990
- 90-7557, Commonwealth Speech (Wilder), 1/15/1990
- 90-7558, Commonwealth Speech (Wilder), 1/15/1990
- 90-7560, Before and After Prayer Service Inauguration Reception at St. Paul's, 1/13/1990
- 90-7561, Jefferson Hotel: pinning of flowers learning for motorcade, and passing mansion keys, 1/13/1990
- 90-7562, Staging area before taking oath of office, 1/13/1990
- 90-7563, Capitol window view of parade and taking oath, 1/13/1990
- 90-7565, 1st Luncheon at the Mansion, 1/13/1990
- 90-7566, 1st Luncheon at the Mansion, 1/13/1990
- 90-7567, Governor with children before Inaugural Ball, 1/13/1990
- 90-7568, Inauguration Weekend Reception at the Mansion, 1/14/1990
- 90-7569, Governor Wilder 1st address to Joint Session of General Assembly, 1/15/1990
- 90-7570, Prayer Service St. Paul's and Opening of the General Assembly, 1/13-15/1990
- 90-7571, Governor Wilder Addresses Joint Session of General Assembly, 1/15/1990
- 90-7575, Governor Wilder accepting car keys, 1/11/1990
- 90-7612, Proclamation signing for Virginia School Board Association, 1/22/1990
- 90-7613, Swearing in Secretary of Commonwealth, 1/22/1990
- 90-7615, St. Mary's presentation to Governor Wilder, 1/22/1990
- 90-7617, Japanese delegation with Wilder, 1/23/1990
- 90-7618, World Access Business group with Wilder, 1/23/1990
- 90-7626, 2 Russian miners visit Governor Wilder, 1/24/1990
- 90-7627, Executive Order # 4: Education opportunity for all Virginians signed by Wilder, 1/24/1990
- 90-7633, Ambassador Pacavire from Angola visits Wilder, 1/25/1990
- 90-7634, VSU Alumni present pen set to Wilder-proclamation signed, 1/25/1990
- 90-7635, VSU Alumni present pen set to Wilder-proclamation signed, 1/25/1990
- 90-7636, Sen. Johnny S. Joannov and family visits Wilder, 1/25/1990
- 90-7652, Presentation of letter of appreciation to Sgt. Jeff Howard by Wilder, 1/29/1990
- 90-7655, Leadership Institute visits Wilder, 1/30/1990
- 90-7666, Swearing in Glen Davidson to Virginia Liaison Office Wilder attended, 1/30/1990
- 90-7672, Swearing in Michael Brown to Board of Elections Wilder attends, 2/1/1990
- 90-7678, Proclamation for American Heart Association by Wilder, 2/1/1990
- 90-7679, Delegate Whittington W. Clements and Inter-Coop Students visit Wilder, 2/1/1990
- 90-7709, Giles High School History Team with Wilder, 2/7/1990
- 90-7727, Senator Emilie F. Miller and Fairfax students visit Wilder, 2/8/1990
- 90-7728, National Engineers Week Wilder signs proclamation, 2/8/1990
- 90-7729, Black Legislative Caucus and aides with Wilder, 2/8/1990
- 90-7730, Vocational Education proclamation by Wilder, 2/8/1990
- 90-7731, Delegate C. Richard Cranwell and guests visit Wilder, 2/8/1990
- 90-7744, AARP Letter of Appreciation signed by Wilder, 2/13/1990
- 90-7745, Exceptional children give gifts to Wilder; and he signs proclamation, 2/13/1990
- 90-7756, Life Insurance Week proclamation signed by Wilder, 2/14/1990
- 90-7757A, Virginia School Principals proclamation signed by Wilder, 2/14/1990
- 90-7757B, Virginia School Principals proclamation signed by Wilder, 2/14/1990
- 90-7758, Kiwanis's Club High School Seniors with Wilder, 2/14/1990
- 90-7759, Coalition of Black Women with Wilder, 2/14/1990
- 90-7761, Economic Advisory Commission sworn in by Wilder, 2/15/1990
- 90-7774, Courtesy call Partner in America visiting Wilder, 2/16/1990
- 90-7775, Courtesy call by Dr. Scott to Wilder, 2/16/1990
- 90-7776, Courtesy call by Dr. Scott to Wilder, 2/16/1990
- 90-7777, YMCA Youth Governor visits Wilder, 2/16/1990
- 90-7778, Korean businessmen visits Wilder, 2/16/1990
- 90-7785, Wilder with staff, 2/20/1990
- 90-7786, Easter seal child visits Wilder, 2/20/1990
- 90-7787, Easter seal child visits Wilder, 2/20/1990
- 90-7792, Cabinet members: Secretary of Transportation and Education, 2/20/1990
- 90-7802, Bridgewater College Student with Wilder, 2/22/1990
- 90-7811, Swearing in Easter Vaser as Minority Business Commission, 2/22/1990
- 90-7812, Swearing in Easter Vaser as Minority Business Commission, 2/22/1990
- 90-7822, Press Conference to name new Secretary of Transportation, 2/25/1990
- 90-7824, Press Conference to name new Secretary of Transportation, 2/25/1990
- 90-7825, Community Affairs Inova Health System Visits Wilder, 2/28/1990
- 90-7828, Wilder visits display at General Assembly Building, 2/28/1990
- 90-7829, Wilder visits Black History Month display at State Library, 2/28/1990
- 90-7842, Wilder opens DMV Mobile License Vehicle, 2/28/1990
- 90-7844, African America Labor group visits Wilde, 3/1/1990
- 90-7845, Wilder signs Virginia Energy Education Day, 3/1/1990
- 90-7846, Del. Ford C. Quiller delegation with Wilder, 3/1/1990
- 90-7847, Intern Student visit Wilder, 3/1/1990
- 90-7850, Group photo of Senate pages, 3/2/1990
- 90-7853, Wilder signs House Bill 103 sponsored by Del. A. Sumit, 3/2/1990
- 90-7854, Del. James F. Almand brings students to visit Wilder, 3/2/1990
- 90-7867, Congressional members & Legislative members meet with Wilder, 3/5/1990
- 90-7868, Congressional members & Legislative members meet with Wilder, 3/5/1990
- 90-7873, Wilder sign House Lt. Governor Beyer, 3/5/1990
- 90-7880, Photo of 2nd floor Governors Mansion before & during construction, 3/6/1990
- 90-7881, Photo of 2nd floor Governors Mansion before & during construction, 3/6/1990
- 90-7882, Photo of 2nd floor Governors Mansion before & during construction, 3/6/1990
- 90-7892, Pages have dinner with Wilder at the Mansion, 3/7/1990
- 90-7898, Wilder signs certificates: Coast Guard Week, 3/8/1990
- 90-7899, Wilder signs certificates: National Wildlife Week, 3/8/1990
- 90-7906, Head Shoulder Rick Walton Guy Horsley, 3/8/1990
- 90-7908, Photos of flooring at Governor's Mansion, 3/9/1990
- 90-7909, Photos of flooring at Governor's Mansion, 3/9/1990
- 90-7913, Shamrock Queen visits with Governor Wilder, 3/9/1990
- 90-7914, Certificate of Recognition Naval Reserves, 3/9/1990
- 90-7915, George Mason portrait and Wilder, 3/9/1990
- 90-7918, USAA Manufacture Corporation visits Wilder, 3/9/1990
- 90-7919, House of Delegates staff photo, 3/9/1990
- 90-7920, Delegate Cranwell and guest visits Wilder, 3/9/1990
- 90-7923, Governor Wilder signing bills, 3/10/1990
- 90-8111, Presentation to Joyce Wilson by Jay Shropshire by Wilder, 3/16/1990
- 90-8112, Presentation to Joyce Wilson by Jay Shropshire by Wilder, 3/16/1990
- 90-8209, Mov Shan Ping Ambassador from Taiwan, 3/19/1990
- 90-8210, Mov Shan Ping Ambassador from Taiwan, 3/19/1990
- 90-8215, Portrait Larry Framme, 3/21/1990
- 90-8218, Management Intern Program, 3/21/1990
- 90-8219, Ameurop Council Relation Foundation awards to children by Wilder, 3/21/1990
- 90-8220, Ameurop Council Relation Foundation awards to children by Wilder, 3/21/1990
- 90-8223, Certificate for Year Airborne, 3/22/1990
- 90-8224, Certificate of Recognition of the National Consumer Week, 3/22/1990
- 90-8225, Portrait Col. Robert L. Suthard Secretary of Public Safety, 3/22/1990
- 90-8249, Presentation of group of books to Governor Wilder, 3/28/1990
- 90-8322, Manchester Lion's Club Proclamation, 3/30/1990
- 90-8313, Week of Young Child: Governor Conference Room, 4/3/1990
- 90-8314, National Safe Boating Week, 4/3/1990
- 90-8315, Richmond Area Marketer Award Certificate, 4/3/1990
- 90-8323, Keep Virginia Beautiful, 4/4/1990
- 90-8325, Stop Child Abuse Dept. of Social Services, 4/4/1990
- 90-8324, American Home Week, 4/4/1990
- 90-8326, Close-ups of floor in Governor's Mansion plus wide angle, 4/4/1990
- 90-8327, Close-ups of floor in Governor's Mansion plus wide angle, 4/4/1990
- 90-8328, Close-ups of floor in Governor's Mansion plus wide angle, 4/4/1990
- 90-8329, Close-ups of floor in Governor's Mansion plus wide angle, 4/4/1990
- 90-8346, Governor Wilder signs a house bill, 4/10/1990
- 90-8347, Students from St. Bridget's school visit with Governor Wilder, 4/10/1990
- 90-8348, Students from St. Bridget's school visit with Governor Wilder, 4/10/1990
- 90-8349, Governor Wilder signs a house bill, 4/10/1990
- 90-8353, Students from Petersburg Elementary visits Governor Wilder, 4/11/1990
- 90-8354, German Exchange students visits Governor Wilder, 4/11/1990
- 90-8356, Delegate Shirley Cooper and students visits Governor Wilder in the white chambers, 4/11/1990
- 90-8375, French Exchange students visits Governor Wilder, 4/12/1990
- 90-8379, Governor Wilder kicks off the Savings Bond Campaign for state employees, 4/13/1990
- 90-8380, Governor Wilder kicks off the Savings Bond Campaign for state employees, 4/13/1990
- 90-8381, Governor Wilder kicks off the Savings Bond Campaign for state employees, 4/13/1990
- 90-8390, United Savings Bond kick-off, 4/13/1990
- 90-8392, Governor Wilder working in his office at the Capitol, 4/13/1990
- 90-8393, Jimmy Reamy and Governor Wilder: Governor's office Fire Service Board, 4/13/1990
- 90-8411, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8412, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8413, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8414, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8415, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8416, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8417, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8418, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8418, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8420, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8421, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8422, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8423, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8424, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8425, Governor's Drug Summit, 4/16-17/1990
- 90-8448, Governor Wilder signs HB 86, 4/18/1990
- 90-8449, Governor Wilder signs HB 1100, 4/18/1990
- 90-8451, Governor Wilder signs SB 335, 4/18/1990
- 90-8452, Governor's Conference Room: Senate Bill 150 Pediatrics, 4/18/1990
- 90-8453, Governor Wilder signs SB 333, 4/18/1990
- 90-8454, Governor Wilder signs 464-465, 4/18/1990
- 90-8455, Governor Wilder: Bill signing Senate Bill 101, 4/18/1990
- 90-8456, Governor Wilder signs HB 108, 4/18/1990
- 90-8457, Signing House Bill 626 Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 4/18/1990
- 90-8458, Governor Wilder signs SB 479, 481, 483, and 484, 4/18/1990
- 90-8459, Senate Bill 467 signing: Senator Emilie Miller, 4/18/1990
- 90-8460, Governor Wilder signs HB 627, 4/18/1990
- 90-8461, Governor Wilder signs HB 357, 4/18/1990
- 90-8462, Governor Wilder signs HB 1096, 4/18/1990
- 90-8463, Courtesy Call of College Personnel, 4/18/1990
- 90-8467, Arthur Ashe visits with Governor Wilder, 4/18/1990
- 90-8468, Arthur Ashe visits with Governor Wilder, 4/18/1990
- 90-8475, Governor Wilder signs CFR for National Boys and Girls Club, 4/19/1990
- 90-8476, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Law Day, 4/19/1990
- 90-8477, Governor Wilder signs CFR for National Organ Tissue Donor Awareness, 4/19/1990
- 90-8478, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Extension Homemaker's Week, 4/19/1990
- 90-8500, Courtesy Call from Dr. Verkuic, President of William and Mary, and visits with Governor Wilder, 4/23/1990
- 90-8501, Courtesy Call from Governor of St. Eustatuis and Honorable and Mrs. Alvin Temmer visits with Governor Wilder, 4/23/1990
- 90-8509, Governor Wilder signs CFR and visits with Holocaust survivors, 4/24/1990
- 90-8510, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Fetal Awareness Week, 4/24/1990
- 90-8511, Governor Wilder visits with students in the Old Senate Chambers, 4/24/1990
- 90-8512, King's Daughters Hospital and Delegate Jerrauld C. Jones makes a presentation to Governor Wilder, 4/24/1990
- 90-8517, Bill signing HB 1055: Clean Air Act, 4/25/1990
- 90-8518, Honorary Membership Theta Psi Chapter Covington, Va. Group presentation to Governor Wilder, 4/25/1990
- 90-8528, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Eastern Shore, 4/26/1990
- 90-8529, Courtesy call from Pre-Med students and they visit with Governor Wilder, 4/26/1990
- 90-8530, Courtesy call from the Polish Delegation and they visit with Governor Wilder, 4/26/1990
- 90-8546, Governor Wilder signs CFR for the City of Harrisonburg, 4/27/1990
- 90-8547, Students from Laurel Ford School visit with Governor Wilder, 4/27/1990
- 90-8548, Casual photos of Governor Wilder, 4/27/1990
- 90-8557, Courtesy Call Minister Kimura, Embassy of Japan visits with Governor Wilder, 4/27/1990
- 90-8572, Governor Wilder signs CFR for National Nursing Home Week, 5/1/1990
- 90-8573, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Week of the Nurse, 5/1/1990
- 90-8574, Governor Wilder signs CFR Manufactured Housing Month, 5/1/1990
- 90-8575, Governor Wilder signs CFR Certificate of Rec. Hospital Pharmacy Week, 5/1/1990
- 90-8576, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Volunteer Rescue Squad Week, 5/1/1990
- 90-8577, Courtesy call at the Governor's Office, 5/1/1990
- 90-8578, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Secretary's Week, 5/1/1990
- 90-8579, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Kiddies Week, 5/3/1990
- 90-8580, Governor Wilder signs SB 83, 188, 5/3/1990
- 90-8583, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Egg Council, 4/30/1990
- 90-8612, Governor Wilder signs HB 129, 560, 5/3/1990
- 90-8613, Governor Wilder signs HB188, 5/3/1990
- 90-8614, Governor Wilder signs HB 310, 5/3/1990
- 90-8615, Governor Wilder signs SB 179, 332, 5/3/1990
- 90-8618, Governor Wilder signs HB 56, 5/3/1990
- 90-8619, Governor Wilder signs HB 176, 5/3/1990
- 90-8620, Governor Wilder signs HB 461, 5/3/1990
- 90-8621, Governor Wilder signs HB 674, 5/3/1990
- 90-8622, Governor Wilder signs HB 808, 5/3/1990
- 90-8623, Governor Wilder signs 839, 5/3/1990
- 90-8624, Governor Wilder signs SB 204, 5/3/1990
- 90-8625, Governor Wilder signs SB 235, 5/3/1990
- 90-8644, Governor Wilder signs HB 678, 5/7/1990
- 90-8645, Students from R.C. Logan School visits with Governor Wilder at Capitol, 5/8/1990
- 90-8646, Governor Wilder presents a plaque to the Nurse of the Year, 5/8/1990
- 90-8647, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Foster Care Week, 5/8/1990
- 90-8648, MS Awards are presented by Governor Wilder, 5/8/1990
- 90-8649, Governor Wilder presents a scholarship to Presoila B. Lapada Jr., 5/8/1990
- 90-8650, Governor Wilder presents a scholarship to Presoila B. Lapada Jr., 5/8/1990
- 90-8682, Little Miss Poppie makes a visit to Governor Wilder, 5/9/1990
- 90-8688, Governor Wilder signs a CFR for Working Women Awareness Week, 5/11/1990
- 90-8690, Governor Wilder presents awards to Correction Officers, 5/11/1990
- 90-8693, Governor Wilder in the State airplane, 5/10/1990
- 90-8694, Governor Wilder in the State airplane, 5/10/1990
- 90-8709, Governor Wilder signs SB 253, 5/15/1990
- 90-8718, John Phellips presents 2 photographs to Governor Wilder, 5/16/1990
- 90-8719, Louise Briehl presents a painting to Governor Wilder, 5/16/1990
- 90-8720, Exchange Rotarians and Richmond Rotarians visits with Governor Wilder, 5/16/1990
- 90-8725, A group from Roanoke made a courtesy call on Governor Wilder, 5/17/1990
- 90-8726, Governor Wilder signs CFR for National Insurance Week, 5/17/1990
- 90-8727, Governor Wilder signs a CFR for Older Virginians, 5/17/1990
- 90-8774, Governor Wilder signs a CFR for Virginia Rivers Month, 5/24/1990
- 90-8775, Governor Wilder signs a CFR for Head Start Day, 5/24/1990
- 90-8776, Governor Wilder signs a CFR for Arthritis Awareness Week, 5/24/1990
- 90-8777, Governor Wilder signs a CFR for Month of the Child, 5/24/1990
- 90-8778, Governor Wilder attends a press conference for VASAPA, 5/24/1990
- 90-8779, Governor Wilder attends a press conference for VASAPA, 5/24/1990
- 90-8780, Governor Wilder signs HB 511, 5/24/1990
- 90-8781, Governor's Office Conference Room: House Bill signing 91, 5/24/1990
- 90-8782, Governor Wilder signs HB 1117, 5/24/1990
- 90-8783, EPU Promotion Party, 5/24/1990
- 90-8784, EPU Promotion Party, 5/24/1990
- 90-8785, EPU Promotion Party, 5/24/1990
- 90-8786, EPU Promotion Party, 5/24/1990
- 90-8787, EPU Promotion Party, 5/24/1990
- 90-8798, Old Senate Chamber Courtesy Call, 5/25/1990
- 90-8799, South African lawyer visits Governor Wilder, 5/25/1990
- 90-8806, Governor Wilder has a press conference and names people to committee, 5/30/1990
- 90-8829, Governor Wilder has a press conference and names people to committee, 5/30/1990
- 90-8846, Miss Teenage Virginia visits with Governor Wilder, 5/31/1990
- 90-8847, Miss Teenage Virginia visits with Governor Wilder, 5/31/1990
- 90-8854, Angola Delegation visits with Governor Wilder, 5/31/1990
- 90-8877, Portrait of Lt. Governor Donald Beyers, 6/4/1990
- 90-8878, Portrait of Lt. Governor Donald Beyers, 6/4/1990
- 90-8882, Governor Wilder has the Governor's Fellows Picnic at the Mansion, 6/4/1990
- 90-8883, Governor Wilder has the Governor's Fellows Picnic at the Mansion, 6/4/1990
- 90-8884, Governor Wilder has the Governor's Fellows Picnic at the Mansion, 6/4/1990
- 90-8889, Governor Wilder visits with AAA Poster Winners, 6/5/1990
- 90-8898, The Ambassador from Japan visits with Governor Wilder, 6/7/1990
- 90-8905, Finnish Executive presents the Governor Wilder a gift, 6/7/1990
- 90-8930, Passport of Secretary of Public Safety Robert Suthard and Mrs Robert Suthard, 6/8/1990
- 90-8943, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Safety Week, 6/12/1990
- 90-8944, Governor Wilder signs Independence for Richmond from violence, 6/12/1990
- 90-8946, Governor Wilder presents achievement awards from the State Library, 6/12/1990
- 90-8947, Governor Wilder presents awards for Drug Free Schools, 6/12/1990
- 90-8948, Governor Wilder presents awards for Drug Free Schools, 6/12/1990
- 90-9001, Prince Bandar bin Sultan bin Adbulaziz from Saudi Arabia visits with Governor Wilder, 6/21/1990
- 90-9002, Winners of the American Co-Ed pageant visits with Governor Wilder, 6/21/1990
- 90-9034, Governor Wilder holds 5th Open House for the citizen of Northern Virginia at George Mason University, 11/10/1990
- 90-9060, People from the PKU party came to visit Governor Wilder, 6/29/1990
- 90-9063, Virginia Federation of Women Clubs presented a gift to Governor Wilder, 7/2/1990
- 90-9064, Andy Fox makes a visit to Governor Wilder, 7/2/1990
- 90-9065, Governor Wilder is presented United States Flag, 7/2/1990
- 90-9080, The Home Builders Association of Virginia meets with Governor Wilder, 7/9/1990
- 90-9081, Allegheny Regional Commission meets with Governor Wilder, 7/9/1990
- 90-9089, Governor Wilder presents a CFR to Peter Decker, 7/11/1990
- 90-9143, Governor Wilder addresses commissions on Health Care, 7/18/1990
- 90-9144, Governor Wilder addresses commission on Health Care, 7/18/1990
- 90-9170, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Weatherization, 7/9/1990
- 90-9171, Mr and Mrs Zapp visits with Governor Wilder, 7/19/1990
- 90-9172, Secretary John Milliken and citizen talk with Governor Wilder about Route 234, 7/19/1990
- 90-9186, Calvin Edwards visits with Governor Wilder, 7/21/1990
- 90-9187, Calvin Edwards visits with Governor Wilder, 7/21/1990
- 90-9188, Calvin Edwards visits with Governor Wilder, 7/21/1990
- 90-9189, Governor Wilder holds an open house for the citizens, 7/21/1990
- 90-9190, Governor Wilder holds an open house for the citizens, 7/21/1990
- 90-9191, Governor Wilder holds an open house for the citizens, 7/21/1990
- 90-9242, Brady Pittman scholarship winners visit with Governor Wilder, 7/24/1990
- 90-9285, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Hoofriagle for Stephanie Lane, 7/27/1990
- 90-9286, Governor Wilder is photographed with the Governor's Fellows, 7/27/1990
- 90-9313, Governor Wilder meets with member of the Legislature on budget, 8/2/1990
- 90-9314, Governor Wilder meets with agency heads about the budget, 8/2/1990
- 90-9354, Governor Wilder signs CFR fir Professional Week, 8/7/1990
- 90-9355, Governor Wilder signs CFR for Cooperative Education, 8/7/1990